[{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":15537,"timeElapsed":193866},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679024448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6325,"timeElapsed":200194},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7624,"timeElapsed":207819},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":24031,"timeElapsed":231853},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679074378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":18269,"timeElapsed":250124},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":10194,"timeElapsed":260318},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5890,"timeElapsed":266210},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":17947,"timeElapsed":284160},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":8114,"timeElapsed":292276},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":40282,"timeElapsed":335088},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5006,"timeElapsed":340094},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":345227},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7629,"timeElapsed":352858},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679181797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4683,"timeElapsed":357543},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5811,"timeElapsed":363355},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3697,"timeElapsed":367053},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4246,"timeElapsed":371301},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":374450},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679229709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":28963,"timeElapsed":405455},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679233030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3321,"timeElapsed":408776},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4416,"timeElapsed":413195},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679240657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3206,"timeElapsed":416403},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679243702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3044,"timeElapsed":419448},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679246860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":422606},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":426639},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3088,"timeElapsed":429728},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274609,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":20624,"timeElapsed":450355},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679282701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8089,"timeElapsed":458447},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679296778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":10529,"timeElapsed":472524},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679301239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4460,"timeElapsed":476985},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679306698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5459,"timeElapsed":482444},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":16452,"timeElapsed":498898},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6981,"timeElapsed":505880},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4459,"timeElapsed":510340},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679338808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4213,"timeElapsed":514554},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679343178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4368,"timeElapsed":518924},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679350895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7716,"timeElapsed":526641},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679361373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":8708,"timeElapsed":537119},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679364928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3553,"timeElapsed":540674},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679371571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":6643,"timeElapsed":547317},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679376956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5383,"timeElapsed":552702},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679381963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5007,"timeElapsed":557709},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679386707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4742,"timeElapsed":562453},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679389725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":565471},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679395732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6004,"timeElapsed":571478},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679403311,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7578,"timeElapsed":579057},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679407101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3788,"timeElapsed":582847},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679425566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":15894,"timeElapsed":601312},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3299,"timeElapsed":604613},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679432493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3624,"timeElapsed":608239},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679436669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4174,"timeElapsed":612415},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679443354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6684,"timeElapsed":619100},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679446922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3567,"timeElapsed":622668},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679450617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3692,"timeElapsed":626363},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679455848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5230,"timeElapsed":631594},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679462414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6563,"timeElapsed":638160},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679480024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":14997,"timeElapsed":655769},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679484960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4935,"timeElapsed":660706},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679488537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3576,"timeElapsed":664283},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679491860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3320,"timeElapsed":667606},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679496682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4821,"timeElapsed":672428},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679499739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3056,"timeElapsed":675485},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679504370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4630,"timeElapsed":680116},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679508412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4040,"timeElapsed":684158},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679512180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3767,"timeElapsed":687926},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679533240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":18701,"timeElapsed":708986},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679538455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5213,"timeElapsed":714201},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679545169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6712,"timeElapsed":720915},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679549608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4439,"timeElapsed":725354},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679554619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5009,"timeElapsed":730364},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679559120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4499,"timeElapsed":734866},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679562442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3321,"timeElapsed":738188},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679566057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3614,"timeElapsed":741803},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679569368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3311,"timeElapsed":745114},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679585856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":15054,"timeElapsed":761602},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679589521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3644,"timeElapsed":765267},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679592963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":768709},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679597160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4194,"timeElapsed":772906},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3361,"timeElapsed":776267},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679604248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3727,"timeElapsed":779994},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679608374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4125,"timeElapsed":784120},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679612174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3798,"timeElapsed":787920},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679615639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3464,"timeElapsed":791384},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679629395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":12281,"timeElapsed":805141},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679632645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3249,"timeElapsed":808391},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679636727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4082,"timeElapsed":812473},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679639843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3115,"timeElapsed":815589},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679642706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":818452},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679646068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3358,"timeElapsed":821813},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679649572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3503,"timeElapsed":825318},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679652813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3240,"timeElapsed":828559},{"subjectID":"09f2jh9faa","prolificID":"67519ff529bffbaed2359e14","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b429ae1d590af2cc237","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679655485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2671,"timeElapsed":831231}]